Hi my name is Keith Fitzpatrick.
This is Hip hop moves for kids and we are going to go over something called the clown.
Now, the clown is one of the dances that started all of the crumbing, that everyone is doing all of a sudden now.
But the clown is kind of different.
So when you do it.
You kind of start you on the real kind of silly and move around.
Move around a lot like clowns.
Clowns are really kind of crazy.
So you start here and your hands are this way.
You do this with your hands.
And as you do that, your body goes up and down.
And up and down.
So when you do it together it's going one, two, three, four.
And you just kind of jump into that.
Boom, boom.
You bounce.
One and two and.
Okay, so that's that part.
Boom and, boom and.
The next part your arms wave here and wave back this way.
When you put it together, you go.
One and here and a wave and a wave.
Okay so again that's here, here wave and wave.
Then you just do it the other way.
Here, here wave and wave.
Okay so, when you put it together, break it down.
Here, here boom, boom, boom.
And that's the clown.